growweedeasy.com 2018-03-11

# Privacy Policy | Grow Weed Easy

You are herePrivacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for GrowWeedEasy.com**

The privacy of our visitors to GrowWeedEasy.com is important to us. 

At GrowWeedEasy.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit GrowWeedEasy.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on GrowWeedEasy.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. However, in most cases you would still be able to visit all pages of the site and read all the free cannabis growing information provided.

**Disclaimers**

Grow Weed Easy only recommends products that we've either personally checked out ourselves, or that come from people we know and trust. For doing so, we may receive a commission.

Nothing on this website should be considered personalized Financial, Legal, or Medical Advice. The contributors to this website and the Grow Weed Easy weekly online magazine grow legally under their local laws but are not lawyers or medical professionals. Any decision to grow marijuana should only be made after consulting with an experienced lawyer or other legal adviser. Any medical decisions should only be made after speaking with a doctor or other medical professional.

Be safe!
